scottiespromotions.com 2011-06-23

# Scotties Facial Tissue

### **Privacy Policy For Irving Tissue, Inc. Website**

 **Last Updated on (November 18, 2002)**

Thank you for visiting our site. This site is owned and operated by, or on behalf of, Irving Tissue, Inc. ("Irving Tissue"). We recognize that many visitors to our site are concerned about the personally identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone number, etc.) they provide to us and how we treat that information. So we've developed a Privacy Policy to address those concerns.

Irving Tissue recognizes its obligation to its customers, community and online visitors to adhere to the highest standards of decency, fairness, and integrity in all its operations. Likewise, Irving Tissue is dedicated to the fundamentals of protecting consumer privacy on the Internet, especially for children.

We may update the Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check frequently for updates by checking the date of "Last Update" at the top of this document. Irving Tissue treats personally identifiable information in a manner consistent with the policy under which it was collected, unless Irving Tissue has your consent to do so differently. The continued use of our site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those changes.

 **What Personally Identifiable Information We Collect**

At our site we don't collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. We may collect your personally identifiable information in order for you to participate in some programs, sweepstakes or other promotions (the "Services") offered on our site, and for the purposes outlined below.

 **What We Use Your Personally Identifiable Information For**  
We use your personally identifiable information: 

  1. for the purpose of providing the Services you request, including using your e-mail and/or your name and phone number, to contact you in connection with providing the Services; 
  2. where you specifically consent to follow-up contacts by Irving Tissue or to be put on our electronic mailing list, to contact you from time to time; and 
  3. for such other purposes to which you may consent from time to time. 

**Disclosure of Your Personally Identifiable Information**

We don't share your personally identifiable information with anyone outside of Irving Tissue and its affiliated and related companies, except to third-party service providers and agents of Irving Tissue which have agreed not to use your personally identifiable information except for specific purposes, as directed by Irving Tissue.

 **Personally Identifiable Information of Minor Children**   
_Important Note to Children_

Before providing your name, address, e-mail address, or any other personally identifiable information to anyone on the Internet, be sure to ask your parents if it's ok.

 _Important Note to Parents_

Irving Tissue is especially mindful of the need to protect the personal privacy of minor children, and our Policy and practices reflect applicable laws and regulations on children's privacy.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 14 years of age. Any communication of personally identifiable information we get that is identified as being from a child under 14 will not be kept by Irving Tissue.

We do, however, permit minor children to communicate with us by e-mail.

 **Deletion of Personally Identifiable Information**

Individuals who provide their personally identifiable information to Irving Tissue can make a written request for deletion of such information from our database at any time by sending a letter to Irving Tissue, Inc., 25 Burlington Mall Road, Burlington, MA, USA, 01803.

 **Cookies**  

Irving Tissue may use "cookie" technology to obtain non-personally identifiable information from its online visitors. Cookies are information files that your Web browser places on your computer when you visit a Web site. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but can be configured not to accept them or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. We do not extract personally identifiable information in this process nor do we provide this information to third parties. Cookies allow us to customize your user interface to speed up the navigation process and to make the site experience more efficient. If your browser is configured to reject cookies, you will not be able to use the features of our site.

We use a temporary session cookie to enable you to use some of our interactive features. These temporary cookies are eliminated when you exit your browser. Another type of cookie can be stored on your computer by your browser. When you log in, this type of cookie tells us whether you've visited us before or are a new visitor. We do use the cookie to help us identify site features in which you have the greatest interest so that we can provide more of what you may want.

 **Links**

While we try to ensure that our site only links to sites that share our high standards of decency, fairness, and integrity, Irving Tissue is not responsible for the contents of any such linked pages or any other pages not under its control and/or part of our site. Irving Tissue makes no representation or warranty regarding, and does not endorse, any linked Web sites, the information appearing thereon or any of the products or services described, other than with respect to our site.

 **Summary**

As in our other business operations, Irving Tissue approaches our communications on the Internet with respect for, and commitment to, individual privacy rights, concern, and respect for the different sensibilities of our consumers. We support active self-regulation of this new environment to ensure that responsible marketers can maintain the right to use all communication media to interact with its consumers.

 **Acceptance of our Privacy Policy**

By using our Web site you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
